Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 2.480 - Technical Services Department - Post-Cataloging Division., 1967-1972.; 893571 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- 2.490 - Theater Arts Library., 1968-1972.; 893570 (Box 183, Folder 3)
- 2.510AC - VM - University Research Library., 1967-1972.; 893569 (Box 183, Folder 4-5)
- 2.510UI - UIIMove - University Research Library., 1967-1973.; 893568 (Box 183, Folder 6)
- 2.515 - Visitors - general correspondence., 1966-1972.; 893567 (Box 184, Folder 1-4)
- 5.000 - A - miscellaneous., 1972-1973.; 893566 (Box 184, Folder 5)
- 5.015 - Arizona, University of and Arizona State University., 1972-1973.; 893565 (Box 184, Folder 6)
- 5.025 - B - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893564 (Box 184, Folder 7)
- 5.055 - C - miscellaneous., 1967-1973.; 893563 (Box 184, Folder 8)
- 5.063 - California Library Network., 1971-1973.; 893562 (Box 184, Folder 9)
- 5.064 - California State Library., 1970-1972.; 893561 (Box 184, Folder 10)
- 5.065 - California State University and Colleges - general correspondence., 1970-1973.; 893560 (Box 184, Folder 11)
- 5.070 - California State University and Colleges - CSU Northridge., 1971-1973.; 893559 (Box 184, Folder 12)
- 5.105 - California State University and Colleges - intersegmental library cooperation., 1972-1973.; 893558 (Box 185, Folder 1)
- 5.108 - Center for Research Libraries., 1970-1976.; 893557 (Box 185, Folder 2-6)
- 5.108 - Center for Research Libraries., 1970-1976.; 893556 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- 5.115 - Chicago, University of., 1970-1973.; 893555 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- 5.125 - Claremont Colleges., 1970-1973.; 893554 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- 5.135 - Colorado, University of., 1972.; 893553 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- 5.140 - Columbia University., 1970-1973.; 893552 (Box 186, Folder 5)
- 5.145 - Cornell University., 1969-1973.; 893551 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- 5.160 - D - miscellaneous., 1971-1972.; 893550 (Box 186, Folder 7)
- 5.175 - E - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893549 (Box 186, Folder 8)
- 5.185 - F - miscellaneous., 1971-1973.; 893548 (Box 186, Folder 9)
- 5.187 - Federal Records Center., 1972.; 893547 (Box 186, Folder 10)
- 5.210 - Foreign universities, libraries, institutions - general., 1971-1973.; 893546 (Box 186, Folder 11-26)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Australia., 1970-1971.; 893545 (Box 186, Folder 27)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Belgium., 1972.; 893544 (Box 186, Folder 28)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Canada., 1970-1973.; 893543 (Box 186, Folder 29)
- 5.210 - Foreign - England., 1970-1973.; 893542 (Box 186, Folder 30)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Germany., 1972.; 893541 (Box 186, Folder 31)
- 5.210 - Foreign - India., 1971.; 893540 (Box 186, Folder 32)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Iran., 1970.; 893539 (Box 186, Folder 33)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Israel., 1973.; 893538 (Box 186, Folder 34)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Italy., 1973.; 893537 (Box 186, Folder 35)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Japan., 1970.; 893536 (Box 186, Folder 36)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Netherlands., 1972-1973.; 893535 (Box 186, Folder 37)
- 5.210 - Foreign - New Zealand., 1970-1971.; 893534 (Box 186, Folder 38)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Philippines., 1971.; 893533 (Box 186, Folder 39)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Portugal., 1971.; 893532 (Box 186, Folder 40)
- 5.210 - Foreign - Scotland., 1971.; 893531 (Box 186, Folder 41)
- 5.215 - G - miscellaneous., 1971-1973.; 893530 (Box 186, Folder 42)
- 5.220 - H - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893529 (Box 186, Folder 43)
- 5.225 - Harvard University., 1970-1973.; 893528 (Box 186, Folder 44)
- 5.240 - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of., 1970-1971.; 893527 (Box 186, Folder 45)
- 5.250 - Huntington Library., 1970-1973.; 893526 (Box 186, Folder 46)
- 5.255 - I - miscellaneous., 1970-1974.; 893525 (Box 186, Folder 47)
- 5.265 - Illinois, University of., 1970-1973.; 893524 (Box 186, Folder 48)
- 5.265 - Indiana University and Indiana State College., 1970-1972.; 893523 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- 5.275 - J - miscellaneous., 1971.; 893522 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- 5.285 - K - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893521 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- 5.300 - L - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893520 (Box 187, Folder 4)
- 5.305 - Library of Congress., 1967-1973.; 893519 (Box 187, Folder 5-7)
- 5.306 - Library of Congress - MARC (Machine-Readable Cataloging)., 1969-1974.; 893518 (Box 187, Folder 8)
- 5.306 - Library of Congress - MARC., 1966-1969.; 893517 (Box 187, Folder 9-10)
- 5.307 - Library of Congress - NPAC (National Program for Acquisitions and Cataloging)., 1966-1973.; 893516 (Box 187, Folder 11)
- 5.308 - Library of Congress - PL-480 (Public Law)., 1966-1973.; 893515 (Box 188, Folder 1-2)
- 5.320 - Los Angeles Public Library., 1970-1971.; 893514 (Box 188, Folder 3)
- 5.330 - M - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893513 (Box 188, Folder 4)
- 5.340 - Massachusetts Institute of Technology., 1968-1971.; 893512 (Box 188, Folder 5)
- 5.345 - Michigan, University of and Michigan State University., 1971-1972.; 893511 (Box 188, Folder 6)
- 5.345 - Minnesota, University of., 1970-1972.; 893510 (Box 188, Folder 7)
- 5.370 - N- miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893509 (Box 188, Folder 8)
- 5.375 - National Argiculture Library., 1970.; 893508 (Box 188, Folder 9)
- 5.380 - National Library of Medicine., 1971.; 893507 (Box 188, Folder 10)
- 5.400 - New York Public Library., 1971-1972.; 893506 (Box 188, Folder 11)
- 5.405 - New York University and State University of New York., 1971-1973.; 893505 (Box 188, Folder 12)
- 5.410 - North Carolina, University of., 1971-1973.; 893504 (Box 188, Folder 13)
- 5.415 - Northwestern University., 1971-1973.; 893503 (Box 188, Folder 14)
- 5.420 - O - miscellaneous., 1970-1972.; 893502 (Box 188, Folder 15)
- 5.435 - Ohio State University., 1970-1973.; 893501 (Box 188, Folder 16)
- 5.440 - Oregon, University of and Oregon State University., 1970-1973.; 893500 (Box 188, Folder 17)
- 5.445 - P - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893499 (Box 189, Folder 1)
- 5.450 - Pennsylvania, University of and Pennsylvania State University., 1972-1974.; 893498 (Box 189, Folder 2)
- 5.455 - Pittsburgh, University of., 1971-1973.; 893497 (Box 189, Folder 3)
- 5.460 - Princeton University., 1972-1973.; 893496 (Box 189, Folder 4)
- 5.470 - Q - miscellaneous., 1933.; 893495 (Box 189, Folder 5)
- 5.475 - R - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893494 (Box 189, Folder 6)
- 5.478 - Rutgers University., 1970-1973.; 893493 (Box 189, Folder 7)
- 5.480 - S - miscellaneous., 1970-1971.; 893492 (Box 189, Folder 8)
- 5.510 - Southern California, University of., 1970-1973.; 893491 (Box 189, Folder 9)
- 5.515 - Stanford University., 1970-1973.; 893490 (Box 189, Folder 10)
- 5.540 - T - miscellaneous., 1971-1973.; 893489 (Box 189, Folder 11)
- 5.550 - Texas, University of., 1970-1972.; 893488 (Box 189, Folder 12)
- 5.570 - Utah, University of., 1970-1973.; 893487 (Box 189, Folder 13)
- 5.575 - V - miscellaneous., 1972-1973.; 893486 (Box 189, Folder 14)
- 5.585 - W - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893485 (Box 189, Folder 15)
- 5.590 - Washington, University of., 1970-1971.; 893484 (Box 189, Folder 16)
- 5.595 - Washington University (St. Louis)., 1969-1972.; 893483 (Box 189, Folder 17)
- 5.600 - WICHE (Western Interstate Commission on Higher Education)., 1970.; 893482 (Box 189, Folder 18)
- 5.605 - Wisconsin, University of., 1970-1973.; 893481 (Box 189, Folder 19)
- 5.615 - Yale University., 1971.; 893480 (Box 189, Folder 20)
- 6.205 - Statewide Advisory Committee on Automation., 1969.; 893479 (Box 189, Folder 21)
- 6.210 - Statewide Alumni Associations, Library Schools., 1969.; 893478 (Box 189, Folder 22)
- 6.230 - Statewide Committee on Research., 1965-1967.; 893477 (Box 189, Folder 23)
- 6.250 - Statewide Institute of Library Research., 1971-1977.; 893476 (Box 189, Folder 24-25)
- 6.257 - Statewide Institute of Library Research - Hayes-Shoffner Proposal., 1966-1969.; 893475 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
- 6.270 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - general., 1965-1972.; 893474 (Box 190, Folder 3-7)
- 6.272 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - Consultant., 1970-1973.; 893473 (Box 190, Folder 8)
- 6.274 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - Cost Benefit Study., 1970-1972.; 893472 (Box 190, Folder 9)
- 6.276 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - documentation., 893471 (Box 191, Folder 1-3)
- 6.278 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - Feasibility Phase., 1970-1971.; 893470 (Box 191, Folder 4)
- 6.279 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - Order Requirements Task Team., 1971.; 893469 (Box 191, Folder 5)
- 6.280 - Statewide Library Systems Development Program - Program Review Committee., 1969-1974.; 893468 (Box 191, Folder 6)
- 6.300 - Library Council - general., 1965-1969.; 893467 (Box 192, Folder 1-5)
- 6.300 - Library Council - general, 1965-1969; 893466 (Box 193, Folder 1-3)
- 6.310 - Library Council - Building Committee, 1964-1965; 893465 (Box 193, Folder 4)
- 6.320 - Library Council - Executive Committee, 1961-1964; 893464 (Box 193, Folder 5)
- 6.322 - Library Council - insurance, 1970-1971; 893463 (Box 193, Folder 6)
- 6.330 - Library Council - Personnel SubCommittee, 1964-1975; 893462 (Box 193, Folder 7)
- 6.347 - Library Council - APPRB's Library Task Force (Academic Planning and Program Review Board)., 1962-1975.; 893461 (Box 194, Folder 1)
- 6.350 - Library Council - Provost's Office., 1965-1975.; 893460 (Box 194, Folder 2)
- 7.010 - Academic Senate (for Senate Library Committee see 2.280)., 1962-1973.; 893459 (Box 194, Folder 3)
- 7.014 - Academic staff organization., 1972-1973.; 893458 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- 7.020 - African Studies Center., 1972-1973.; 893457 (Box 194, Folder 5)
- 7.025 - Afro-American Center., 1969-1973.; 893456 (Box 194, Folder 6)
- 7.030 - Argiculture, College of., 1971.; 893455 (Box 194, Folder 7)
- 7.040 - Alumni and Development Office., 1970.; 893454 (Box 194, Folder 8)
- 7.045 - Alumni and Association (includes UCLA Foundation)., 1972-1973.; 893453 (Box 194, Folder 9)
- 7.047 - American Indian Cultural Center., 1970-1973.; 893452 (Box 194, Folder 10)
- 7.057TP - American Indian Culture Center Treaties Project., 1971-1975.; 893451 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- 7.060 - Architecture and Urban Planning, School of., 1970-1972.; 893450 (Box 195, Folder 2)
- 7.080 - Art galleries., 1971.; 893449 (Box 195, Folder 3)
- 7.083 - Asian Amercian Studies Center., 1970-1973; 1970-1976.; 893448 (Box 195, Folder 4-5)
- 7.085 - Astronomy, Department of 1973., 893447 (Box 195, Folder 6)
- 7.090 - ASUCLA - general., 1972.; 893446 (Box 195, Folder 7)
- 7.093 - Auxiliary and service enterprises (coordinates residence halls, guest house, parking, central garage)., 1971-1973.; 893445 (Box 195, Folder 8)
- 7.098 - Biomathematics., 1971.; 893444 (Box 195, Folder 9)
- 7.110 - Brain Research Institute., 1970.; 893443 (Box 195, Folder 10)
- 7.115 - Bruin., 1970-1972.; 893442 (Box 195, Folder 11)
- 7.140 - Business Services., 1969-1973.; 893441 (Box 195, Folder 12)
- 7.142 - Campus Activities Service Office (CASO)., 1970-1973.; 893440 (Box 195, Folder 13)
- 7.144 - Campus Computing Network., 1970-1973.; 893439 (Box 195, Folder 14)
- 7.155 - Chancellor's Office., 1969-1973.; 893438 (Box 195, Folder 15)
- 7.157 - Chancellor's Office - administrative calendar., 1969-1972.; 893437 (Box 196, Folder 1)
- 7.161 - Chancellor's Office - blood drive/United Crusade., 1970-1971.; 893436 (Box 196, Folder 2)
- 7.163 - Chancellor's Office - Committee appointments., 1966-1971.; 893435 (Box 196, Folder 3)
- 7.165 - Chancellor's Office - correspondence., 1964-1973.; 893434 (Box 196, Folder 4-6)
- 7.172 - Chancellor's Office - equal employment oppurtUnity (includes Committee on Status of Women - see personnel files for affirmative action 1.003)., 1968-1973.; 893433 (Box 196, Folder 7)
- 7.175 - Chancellor's Office - International and Comparative Studies., 1965-1967.; 893432 (Box 196, Folder 8)
- 7.180 - Chancellor's Office - memos., 1969; 1964-1973.; 893431 (Box 196, Folder 9-10)
- 7.185 - Chancellor's Office - Naming Building and Street Committee., 1967-1972.; 893430 (Box 196, Folder 11)
- 7.190 - Chancellor's Office - Planning Office., 1962-1973.; 893429 (Box 196, Folder 12)
- 7.201 - Chicano Studies Center., 1970-1973; 1970-1976.; 893428 (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
- 7.205 - Classics Department., 1970-1972.; 893427 (Box 197, Folder 3)
- 7.210 - Committee on Fine Arts Productions and Public Lectures., 1972.; 893426 (Box 197, Folder 4)
- 7.220 - Communications Center., 1970-1973.; 893425 (Box 197, Folder 5)
- 7.250 - Dentistry, School of., 1972-1973.; 893424 (Box 197, Folder 6)
- 7.260 - Education, School of., 1970-1973.; 893423 (Box 197, Folder 7)
- 7.262 - Emeriti Office., 1971-1973.; 893422 (Box 197, Folder 8)
- 7.270 - English Department., 1970-1973.; 893421 (Box 197, Folder 9)
- 7.275 - Environmental Health and Safety., 1969-1973.; 893420 (Box 197, Folder 10)
- 7.279 - Ethnic Centers (includes Institute in Ethnic Minorities Librarianship)., 1969-1976; 893419 (Box 197, Folder 11-13)
- 7.284 - Extended Studies., 1973.; 893418 (Box 197, Folder 14)
- 7.285 - Extended University., 1973.; 893417 (Box 197, Folder 15)
- 7.285 - Extended University., 1970-1973.; 893416 (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
- 7.300 - Facilities Development and Management (Coordinates Campus Architects and Engineers, Physical Plant, Environmental Health and Safety)., 1970-1973.; 893415 (Box 198, Folder 4)
- 7.310 - Folklore, Department of., 1970.; 893414 (Box 198, Folder 5)
- 7.325 - Geography Department., 1970-1973.; 893413 (Box 198, Folder 6)
- 7.340 - Germanic Languages Department., 1970-1972.; 893412 (Box 198, Folder 7)
- 7.350 - Graduate Division., 1966-1973.; 893411 (Box 198, Folder 8)
- 7.352 - Graduate Students Association., 1970.; 893410 (Box 198, Folder 9)
- 7.360 - History Department., 1970-1973.; 893409 (Box 198, Folder 10)
- 7.381 - Institute of Government and Public Affairs., 1971.; 893408 (Box 198, Folder 11)
- 7.385 - Institute of International and Comparative Studies., 1971-1973.; 893407 (Box 198, Folder 12)
- 7.390 - Inventory Department., 1960-1973.; 893406 (Box 198, Folder 13)
- 7.395 - Italian Department., 1969-1972.; 893405 (Box 198, Folder 14)
- 7.420 - Latin American Center., 1970-1972.; 893404 (Box 198, Folder 15)
- 7.425 - Law, School of., 1972.; 893403 (Box 198, Folder 16)
- 7.435 - Graduate School of Library and Information Science., 1968-1973.; 893402 (Box 198, Folder 17)
- 7.445 - Mail Room., 1970-1973.; 893401 (Box 199, Folder 1)
- 7.451 - Management, Graduate School of., 1970-1973.; 893400 (Box 199, Folder 2)
- 7.455 - Master Plan., 1959-1966; 1972-1973.; 893399 (Box 199, Folder 3-10)
- 7.460 - Mathematics Department., 1973.; 893398 (Box 199, Folder 11)
- 7.461 - Mathematics Department - Graduate Reading Room., 1968-1969.; 893397 (Box 199, Folder 12)
- 7.464 - Media Center (includes Academic Communications Facility)., 1970-1973.; 893396 (Box 199, Folder 13)
- 7.465 - Medicine, School of., 1970-1972.; 893395 (Box 199, Folder 14)
- 7.490 - Music Department., 1966-1973.; 893394 (Box 199, Folder 15)
- 7.500 - National Television Library., 1971-1973.; 893393 (Box 199, Folder 16)
- 7.505 - Near Eastern Center., 1971-1973.; 893392 (Box 200, Folder 1)
- 7.510 - Neuropsychiatric Institute Library., 1973.; 893391 (Box 200, Folder 2)
- 7.512 - New Careers Training Program., 1970.; 893390 (Box 200, Folder 3)
- 7.519 - Nursing, School of., 1973.; 893389 (Box 200, Folder 4)
- 7.525 - Open House., 1969-1970.; 893388 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- 7.530 - Oriental Languages, Department of., 1970-1973.; 893387 (Box 200, Folder 6)
- 7.540 - Parking service., 1970-1973.; 893386 (Box 200, Folder 7)
- 7.543 - Part-time Degree Program., 1970-1971.; 893385 (Box 200, Folder 8)
- 7.558 - Physical plant., 1970-1973.; 893384 (Box 200, Folder 9)
- 7.559 - Custodial services., 1970-1973.; 893383 (Box 200, Folder 10)
- 7.565 - Police Department., 1970-1973.; 893382 (Box 200, Folder 11)
- 7.570 - Political Science Department (includes Public Administration)., 1970-1972.; 893381 (Box 200, Folder 12)
- 7.575 - Publication Services Department., 1970-1973.; 893380 (Box 200, Folder 13)
- 7.585 - Public Affairs - Public Information Office., 1970-1973.; 893379 (Box 200, Folder 14)
- 7.590 - Public Health, School of., 1970.; 893378 (Box 200, Folder 15)
- 7.595 - Purchasing Department., 1970-1973.; 893377 (Box 200, Folder 16)
- 7.610 - Records Management Program., 1964-1973.; 893376 (Box 200, Folder 17)
- 7.615 - Recreation services and facilities., 1969-1971.; 893375 (Box 200, Folder 18)
- 7.627 - Romance Program., 1970.; 893374 (Box 200, Folder 19)
- 7.630 - Russian and East European Studies Center., 1971.; 893373 (Box 200, Folder 20)
- 7.635 - Scandinavian Languages Department., 1970.; 893372 (Box 200, Folder 21)
- 7.673 - Student Educational Policy Commission., 1969-1970.; 893371 (Box 200, Folder 22)
- 7.675 - Summer sessions., 1972.; 893370 (Box 200, Folder 23)
- 7.690 - Theater Arts Department., 1970-1971.; 893369 (Box 200, Folder 24)
- 7.713 - Water Resources Center., 1972-1973.; 893368 (Box 200, Folder 25)
- 9.005 - A - miscellaneous., 1970-1974.; 893367 (Box 201, Folder 1)
- 9.006 - Abel Proposal., 1972-1973.; 893366 (Box 201, Folder 2)
- 9.035 - B - miscellaneous., 1956-1973.; 893365 (Box 201, Folder 3)
- 9.060 - C - miscellaneous., 1968-1977.; 893364 (Box 201, Folder 4-8)
- 9.070 - Carnegie Corporation., 1970-1971.; 893363 (Box 201, Folder 9)
- 9.100 - D - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893362 (Box 201, Folder 10)
- 9.105 - Dawson's Book Shop., 1971-1972.; 893361 (Box 201, Folder 11)
- 9.115 - E - miscellaneous., 1969-1973.; 893360 (Box 201, Folder 12)
- 9.117 - Earthquake., 1971-1973.; 893359 (Box 201, Folder 13)
- 9.125 - F - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893358 (Box 201, Folder 14)
- 9.130 - Fritz, Mrs. Bernadine Szold., 1970-1972.; 893357 (Box 201, Folder 15)
- 9.140 - G - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893356 (Box 201, Folder 16)
- 9.160 - Guggenheim Foundation., 1948-1974.; 893355 (Box 201, Folder 17-19)
- 9.165 - H - miscellaneous., 1967-1973.; 893354 (Box 202, Folder 1)
- 9.175 - Harrassowitz: Otto., 1972.; 893353 (Box 202, Folder 2)
- 9.190 - I - miscellaneous., 1971-1973.; 893352 (Box 202, Folder 3)
- 9.195 - IBM., 1970.; 893351 (Box 202, Folder 4)
- 9.200 - J - miscellaneous., 1971-1972.; 893350 (Box 202, Folder 5)
- 9.210 - K - miscellaneous., 1968-1972.; 893349 (Box 202, Folder 6)
- 9.235 - L - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893348 (Box 202, Folder 7)
- 9.240 - L.A. Times., 1970-1972.; 893347 (Box 202, Folder 8)
- 9.245 - M - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893346 (Box 202, Folder 9)
- 9.270 - Murphy, Franklin D. Associates., 1970-1973.; 893345 (Box 202, Folder 10)
- 9.280 - N - miscellaneous., 1967-1972.; 893344 (Box 202, Folder 11)
- 9.307 - O'Malley C.D., 1970-1972.; 893343 (Box 202, Folder 12)
- 9.310 - P - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893342 (Box 202, Folder 13)
- 9.320 - Powell, Lawrence Clark., 1965-1972.; 893341 (Box 202, Folder 14)
- 9.330 - R - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893340 (Box 202, Folder 15)
- 9.355 - S - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893339 (Box 202, Folder 16)
- 9.380 - Stevens and Brown, B. F., 1971.; 893338 (Box 202, Folder 17)
- 9.395 - System Development Corporation., 1971-1972.; 893337 (Box 202, Folder 18)
- 9.400 - T - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893336 (Box 202, Folder 19)
- 9.415 - U - miscellaneous., 1972-1973.; 893335 (Box 202, Folder 20)
- 9.430 - University Microfilm., 1970-1971.; 893334 (Box 202, Folder 21)
- 9.435 - V - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893333 (Box 202, Folder 22)
- 9.440 - W - miscellaneous., 1970-1973.; 893332 (Box 202, Folder 23)
- 9.460 - Wilson Co., H.W., 1970.; 893331 (Box 202, Folder 24)
- 9.475 - Y - miscellaneous., 1965-1973.; 893330 (Box 202, Folder 25)
- Librarians, Academic Restructuring, 1962-1972; 893329 (Box 203, Folder 1-2)
- Non-academic Re-Classification, 1970-1972; 893328 (Box 203, Folder 3)
- 2.015 - Architecture Library., 1970-1977.; 893326 (Box 204, Folder 1)
- 2.016 - Architecture Library - Neutra Collection., 1975-1976.; 893325 (Box 204, Folder 2)
- 2.020 - Archives (no material)., 893324 (Box 204, Folder 3)
- 2.021 - Archives - theses and dissertations., 893323 (Box 204, Folder 4)
- 2.025 - Art Library., 1973-1976.; 893322 (Box 204, Folder 5)
- 2.026 - Art Library: Elmer Belt Library., 1970-1976.; 893321 (Box 204, Folder 6)
- 2.027 - Art Library - index of Christian art., 1976.; 893320 (Box 204, Folder 7)
- 2.030 - Bibliographers - general., 1973-1976.; 893319 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- 2.030A - African Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893318 (Box 205, Folder 2)
- 2.030ASA - Asian American Bibliographer., 1973-1975.; 893317 (Box 205, Folder 3)
- 2.030G - Germanic Bibliographer., 1975-1976.; 893316 (Box 205, Folder 4)
- 2.030H - Humanities Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893315 (Box 205, Folder 5)
- 2.030IP - Indo. Pacific Bibliographer., 1975.; 893314 (Box 205, Folder 6)
- 2.030JS - Jewish Studies Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893313 (Box 205, Folder 7)
- 2.030LA - Latin American Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893312 (Box 205, Folder 8)
- 2.030MR - Medieval and Renaissance Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893311 (Box 205, Folder 9)
- 2.030NE - Near Eastern Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893310 (Box 205, Folder 10)
- 2.030S - Slavic Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893309 (Box 205, Folder 11)
- 2.030SS - Social Scienecs Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893308 (Box 205, Folder 12)
- 2.030WE - West European Bibliographer., 1973-1976.; 893307 (Box 205, Folder 13)
- 2.035 - Biomedical Library., 1973-1976.; 893306 (Box 205, Folder 14)
- 2.036 - Biomedical Library - Medline., 1972-1974.; 893305 (Box 205, Folder 15)
- 2.037 - Biomedical Library - Regional Medical Library Service., 1973-1975.; 893304 (Box 205, Folder 16)
- 2.039 - Bookbindery., 1973-1975.; 893303 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- 2.040 - Book buying abroad., 1974-1976.; 893302 (Box 206, Folder 2)
- 2.053 - Campbell Book Contest., 1973-1976.; 893301 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- 2.055 - Capital Improvements - major., 1973-1976.; 893300 (Box 206, Folder 4)
- 2.056 - Capital Improvements - minor., 1973-1976.; 893299 (Box 206, Folder 5)
- 2.057 - Catalog supplement., 1973-1976.; 893298 (Box 206, Folder 6)
- 2.060 - Census Bureau depository arrangements., 1973-1975.; 893297 (Box 206, Folder 7)
- 2.060D - Census Bureau Dualabs., 1973-1975.; 893296 (Box 206, Folder 8)
- 2.063 - Center for Information Services., 1973-1975.; 893295 (Box 206, Folder 9-10)
- 2.063 - Center for Information Services., 1973-1975.; 893294 (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
- 2.065 - Chemistry Library., 1973-1976.; 893293 (Box 207, Folder 3)
- 2.070 - Circulation., 1971-1976.; 893292 (Box 207, Folder 4-5)
- 2.070 - MRLC - Machine-readable library card., 1972-1975.; 893291 (Box 208, Folder 1)
- 2.080 - Clark Library., 1973-1976.; 893290 (Box 208, Folder 2)
- 2.081 - Clark Library Committee., 1973-1976.; 893289 (Box 208, Folder 3)
- 2.095 - Collection Development., 1970-1976.; 893288 (Box 208, Folder 4)
- 2.095A - Armenian Collection., 1970-1975.; 893287 (Box 208, Folder 5)
- 2.100 - College Library., 1976.; 893286 (Box 208, Folder 6)
- 2.100 - College Library., 1973-1975; 893285 (Box 209, Folder 1)
- 2.100AV - College Library - audio-visual., 1975-1976.; 893284 (Box 209, Folder 2)
- 2.100RH - Residence Hall libraries., 1971-1975.; 893283 (Box 209, Folder 3)
- 2.110 - Comps., 1973-1976.; 893282 (Box 209, Folder 4)
- 2.115 - Conference arrangements., 1970-1975.; 893281 (Box 209, Folder 5)
- 2.117 - Conser., 1975-1976.; 893280 (Box 209, Folder 6)
- 2.120 - Copyright., 1975-1976; 1972-1976.; 893279 (Box 209, Folder 7)
- 2.120 - Copyright - registration for., 1976.; 893278 (Box 209, Folder 8)
- 2.12T - Data services NY Times Info. Bank., 1974-1975.; 893277 (Box 210, Folder 1)
- 2.127 - Data services., 1975-1976.; 893276 (Box 210, Folder 2)
- 2.130 - Departmental Book and Sound Recording Annual Inventory., 1968-1969.; 893275 (Box 210, Folder 3)
- 2.135 - Duplicate book disposal., 1971-1975.; 893274 (Box 210, Folder 4)
- 2.140 - Education/Psychology Library., 1973-1974.; 893273 (Box 210, Folder 5)